<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">tomhoover [dot] net</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="" />
<updated>2015-01-25T21:46:20-06:00</updated>
<id>/</id>
<author>
  <name>Tom Hoover</name>
  <uri>/</uri>
  <email>tom@tomhoover.net</email>
</author>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most memorable Christmas days in my life.]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/one-of-the-most-memorable-christmas-days-in-my-life/" />
  <id>/one-of-the-most-memorable-christmas-days-in-my-life</id>
  <published>2009-12-26T00:00:00-06:00</published>
  <updated>2009-12-26T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tom Hoover</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>tom@tomhoover.net</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’ve completed what has to be one of the most memorable, although unusual, Christmas days in my life. Our &lt;em&gt;festivities&lt;/em&gt; normally start on Christmas Eve, but this year it didn’t feel like Christmas Eve because Kady was in the hospital. It snowed on Christmas Eve—never done that before. Christmas day festivities would normally start at the crack of dawn, but the family wouldn’t be complete until Kady’s arrival at 1000. Kady had to return to the hospital at 1800, so our time was limited. However…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christmas was a wonderful day, and I have so much for which to be thankful. My wife, kids and grandkids were here. Bridgett’s mom, Linda Woodall, was here. It was Riddick’s first Christmas. We had way too much food, and way too many presents. Although I love food (no kiddin’) and presents, none of that mattered to me—I just looked at how the Lord has blessed me with such a wonderful family. Even though our family time this year was more limited than &lt;em&gt;normal&lt;/em&gt;, I treasured it more than &lt;em&gt;normal&lt;/em&gt;. I know I don’t say it, nor show it enough, but I love my Lord and I love my family!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/one-of-the-most-memorable-christmas-days-in-my-life/&quot;&gt;One of the most memorable Christmas days in my life.&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Tom Hoover at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;tomhoover [dot] net&lt;/a&gt; on December 26, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Prayer]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/my-prayer/" />
  <id>/my-prayer</id>
  <published>2006-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</published>
  <updated>2006-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tom Hoover</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>tom@tomhoover.net</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Lord, I shall not fret about yesterday, for yesterday is no more.  I shall not
fear tomorrow, for tomorrow is yet to come.  So, Lord, at least in some small
way I shall try to deserve today.  Amen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;-Author Unknown&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/my-prayer/&quot;&gt;My Prayer&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Tom Hoover at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;tomhoover [dot] net&lt;/a&gt; on January 29, 2006.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Romans 1:16]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/romans-1-16/" />
  <id>/romans-1-16</id>
  <published>2001-01-01T00:00:00-06:00</published>
  <updated>2001-01-01T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tom Hoover</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>tom@tomhoover.net</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Romans 1:16 &lt;em&gt;For I am not ashamed of the gospel of Christ: for it is the power
of God unto &lt;a href=&quot;http://hisword.net/saved/&quot;&gt;salvation&lt;/a&gt; to every one that believeth; to the Jew
first, and also to the Greek.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/romans-1-16/&quot;&gt;Romans 1:16&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Tom Hoover at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;tomhoover [dot] net&lt;/a&gt; on January 01, 2001.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>

</feed>